<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Clarice D. Aiello</title>
    <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Clarice D. Aiello</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Clarice D. Aiello.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I am interested in how quantum physics informs biology at the nanoscale. 
My future research program will build on my past successes in developing high-performance nanosensors that essentially work due to room-temperature quantum effects under noisy environments, and in modeling physical mechanisms employed by &amp;ldquo;living sensors&amp;rdquo;. I will invest my physics training to unveil, control and harness the advantages of evolutionarily-selected biological sensing occurring at the nanoscale.
You will soon find here my Research, Teaching and Diversity Statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/talks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/awards/</guid>
      <description>Life Sciences Research Foundation Postdoctoral Fellowship
 Project Unraveling the spin physics of in vivo magnetosensing  sponsored by the Gordon and Betty Moore Foundation  Selected to the Rising Stars in Physics Workshop
 Physics Dept., MIT  Graduate Student Award for Extraordinary Teaching and Mentoring
 School of Engineering, MIT  Selected to the Rising Stars in Nuclear Engineering Workshop
 Nuclear Science and Engineering Dept., MIT  Faculty for the Future Fellowship</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/teaching-and-mentoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/teaching-and-mentoring/</guid>
      <description>Instructor for course 6.003 Signals and Systems, MIT  Teaching evaluation: overall rating 6.7 &amp;#47; 7.0  Instructor for Teaching and Learning Laboratory&amp;rsquo;s Teaching Certificate Program, MIT  The 20-hour curriculum covered topics such as course design and best practices in exam writing, lecturing, and building an inclusive classroom
 Promoted to instructor after taking the Certificate
  Organizer and lecturer for Independent Activities Period&amp;rsquo;s course Implementations of Quantum Computing, MIT Teaching assistant for course 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/leadership-and-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/leadership-and-service/</guid>
      <description>Reviewer  for Nature Physics, Nature Communications, Physical Review Letters, Physical Review A
 Co-organizer  (with Prof. Vanessa Huxter, University of Arizona) of the Moore Foundation Workshop on Quantum Biology (2019)
 Elected postdoc representative  at the Faculty Senate Committee for Research, Stanford
 Mediator  40-hour trained by the Institute Resources for Easing Friction and Stress, MIT
 Graduate student representative  at the Institute Committee for Graduate Programs, MIT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outreach</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/outreach/</guid>
      <description>Miscellaneous Foldscope-related events 
 Organized and participated in demos at: Stanford University, the California Academy of Sciences, the San Quentin California state penitentiary and the Intel International Science and Engineering Fair   Miscellaneous science outreach events in the Boston area 
 Assembled and coordinated a team of 6 that built a 6’-tall indoor tornado simulator. The tornado was first exhibited at the kick-off event of the Cambridge Science Festival (project sponsor), subsequently spending one Summer at the MIT museum, and making appearances at MIT outreach events such as the Center for Ultracold Atoms Kids’ Day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/non-academic-interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/non-academic-interests/</guid>
      <description>I firmly believe that scientists (and everybody else!) should be well-rounded individuals.
I have always been a bookworm and thrived in learning languages. I find it befitting that the German word for &amp;ldquo;vocabulary&amp;rdquo; is &amp;ldquo;Wortschatz&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; which literally translates to &amp;ldquo;word treasure&amp;rdquo;. I enjoy writing and wordsmithing.
I have also dabbled in piano and chorale singing; and taken a liking to long-distance running, yoga-ing and meditating.
Finally, I have a serious interest in wine (Wine and Spirit Education Trust Level 3 Award, Boston University&amp;rsquo;s Certificate in Wine Studies, French Wine Scholar).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://web.stanford.edu/~caiello/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>